Mickey and friends hitch a ride on a musical hay wagon.
Get a Horse! is a animation, family, comedy film directed by Lauren MacMullan.
Mickey, Minnie, Horace Horsecollar, and Clarabelle Cow go on a musical
wagon ride until Peg-Leg Pete tries to run them off the road.
Mickey Mouse (voice), played by Walt Disney.
Minnie Mouse (voice), played by Marcellite Garner.
Minnie Mouse (voice), played by Russi Taylor.
Peg-Leg Pete (voice), played by Billy Bletcher.
Peg-Leg Pete (voice), played by Will Ryan.
Additional Voices (voice), played by Bob Bergen.
Get a Horse!
is a 2013 American animated comedy short film produced by Walt Disney
Animation Studios and directed by Lauren MacMullan.
Combining black-and-white hand-drawn animation and color computer animation, the
short features the characters of the late 1920s Mickey Mouse cartoons.
The film features archival recordings of Walt Disney, Billy Bletcher and Marcellite Garner in
their respective posthumous roles as Mickey Mouse, Peg Leg Pete and Minnie Mouse.
Russi Taylor and Will Ryan provide some of Minnie's and Pete's lines (Mickey’s final line "Goodbye, goodbye,
little feller!" is an uncredited line by Jimmy MacDonald sourced from an archival recording.
Disney's voice is also heard as Minnie in one instance crying out "Help!
Help!", though he is uncredited in that role.)
It is the first original Mickey Mouse theatrical animated short since Runaway Brain in 1995, and
the first appearance of Oswald the Lucky Rabbit in a Disney animated production in 85 years, albeit for a split second cameo.
The short was nominated for Best Animated Short Film at the 86th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of mouse, computer animation,
black and white, cartoon mouse, color.
The tone is lighthearted.